[{
    "general knowledge": [{
            "number": 1,
            "question": "What is the name of the man that was struck dead by God for holding the Ark of God from falling?",
            "options": ["Uzzah", "Abner", "Obededom", "Edom"],
            "answer": "Uzzah",
            "verse": "2Sam. 6:6-7"
        },
        {
            "number": 2,
            "question": "Who was the first man in the Bible to get drunk with wine?",
            "options": ["Lot", "Ham", "Noah", "Solomon"],
            "answer": "Noah",
            "verse": "Gen. 9:20-21"
        },
        {
            "number": 3,
            "question": "How old was the oldest man (Methuselah) in the Bible when he died?",
            "options": ["950", "962", "969", "365"],
            "answer": "969",
            "verse": "Gen. 5:27"
        },
        {
            "number": 4,
            "question": "How many wives and concubines did king Solomon have?",
            "options": ["300 wives and 700 concubines", "700 concubines and 300 wives", "700 wives and 300 concubines", "300 concubines and 7000 wives"],
            "answer": "700 wives and 300 concubines",
            "verse": "1Kings 11:3"
        },
        {
            "number": 5,
            "question": "Who handkerchief healed the sick?",
            "options": ["Paul", "John", "Peter", "James"],
            "answer": "Paul",
            "verse": "Acts 19:11-12"
        },

        {
            "number": 6,
            "question": "State the Golden Rule.",
            "options": ["Thy shall not steal", "No sin goes unpunished", "Thy shall love thine neighbor as thyself", "Therefore all things whatsoever ye would that men should do to you: do ye even so to them: for this is the law and the prophets"],
            "answer": "Therefore all things whatsoever ye would that men should do to you: do ye even so to them: for this is the law and the prophets",
            "verse": "Matt. 7:12"
        },

        {
            "number": 7,
            "question": "How many people of Jacob's household went to Egypt?",
            "options": ["17", "12", "13", "70"],
            "answer": "70",
            "verse": "Gen. 46:27"
        },

        {
            "number": 8,
            "question": "What are the names of the two sons' of Joseph?",
            "options": ["Hophni and Phinehas", "Joshua and Caleb", "Ben-ammi and Moab", "Ephraim and Manasseh"],
            "answer": "Ephraim and Manasseh",
            "verse": "Gen. 48:1"
        },

        {
            "number": 9,
            "question": "Who was the youngest King recorded in the Bible?",
            "options": ["Solomon (7 years)", "Jeroboam (7 years)", "Rehoboam (7 years)", "Joash (7 years)"],
            "answer": "Joash (7 years)",
            "verse": "2 Chro. 24:1"
        },

        {
            "number": 10,
            "question": "What was Benjamin's initial name at birth",
            "options": ["Ben-jami", "Ben", "Favor", "Benoni"],
            "answer": "Benoni",
            "verse": "Gen. 35:18"
        }, {
            "number": 11,
            "question": "Where was Moses buried?",
            "options": ["In the valley in the land of Moah. Sepulchre unknown", "In the cave of Malchpelah", "Egypt", "In the Red Sea"],
            "answer": "In the valley in the land of Moah. Sepulchre unknown",
            "verse": "Deut. 34:6"
        }, {
            "number": 12,
            "question": "Who was the first woman prophet?",
            "options": ["Sarah", "Eve", "Rachel", "Miriam"],
            "answer": "Miriam",
            "verse": "Exo. 15:20"
        }, {
            "number": 13,
            "question": "Name the man that was struck dumb by Angel Gabriel throughout his wife pregnancy(9 months) for unbelief.",
            "options": ["Simeon", "Zacharias", "Gideon", "Hezekiah"],
            "answer": "Zacharias",
            "verse": "Luke 1:18-20"
        }, {
            "number": 14,
            "question": "What are the names of the two men who never saw death?",
            "options": ["Joshua and Caleb", "John and Ezekiel", "Moses and Melchizedek", "Enoch and Elijah"],
            "answer": "Enoch and Elijah",
            "verse": "Gen. 5:23-24, 2Kings 2:11"
        }, {
            "number": 15,
            "question": "Whose house was the ark of God kept for 3 months after the death of Uzzah?",
            "options": ["David", "Obededom", "Joab", "Saul"],
            "answer": "Obededom",
            "verse": "2Sam. 6:10-11"
        }, {
            "number": 16,
            "question": "What is the name of Joseph's wife?",
            "options": ["Rebekah", "Esther", "Asenath", "Deborah"],
            "answer": "Asenath",
            "verse": "Gen. 41:45"
        }, {
            "number": 17,
            "question": "What is the second name of Daniel?",
            "options": ["Beltshazzar", "Bethel", "The interpreter", "The Lions' King"],
            "answer": "Beltshazzar",
            "verse": "Daniel 1:7"
        }, {
            "number": 18,
            "question": "Who was Israel first judge",
            "options": ["Samson", "Deborah", "Jephthah", "Othniel"],
            "answer": "Othniel",
            "verse": "Judges 3:9-11"
        },
        {
            "number": 19,
            "question": "What is the name of the king who disallowed Israel's passage during the Exo.?",
            "options": ["King Saul", "King Of Moriah", "King of Edom", "King David"],
            "answer": "King of Edom",
            "verse": "Num. 20:18-21"
        },
        {
            "number": 20,
            "question": "Which of the author of the Bible is also a physician?",
            "options": ["Paul", "Boaz", "Moses", "Luke"],
            "answer": "Luke",
            "verse": "Col.1, 4"
        },
        {
            "number": 21,
            "question": "Who shadow healed the sick?",
            "options": ["Peter", "Paul", "James", "John"],
            "answer": "Peter",
            "verse": "Acts 5:14-15"
        },
        {
            "number": 22,
            "question": "Name the three friends of Job that came to console him?",
            "options": ["Bildad, Eliphaz, Zophar", "Joab, Jashobeam, Eleazer", "Sanballat, Tobiah, Geshen", "Shadrach, Meshach, Abednego"],
            "answer": "Bildad, Eliphaz, Zophar",
            "verse": "Job 4, 8, 11"
        },
        {
            "number": 23,
            "question": "Who is referred to ass the secret disciple of Jesus?",
            "options": ["Joseph who buried Jesus", "Nichodemus", "Zaccheaus", "Blind Bartimaeus"],
            "answer": "Nichodemus",
            "verse": "John 3:1-2"
        },
        {
            "number": 24,
            "question": "Who is the first person in the Bible to defile his father's bed?",
            "options": ["Absalom", "Judah", "Reuben", "Ham"],
            "answer": "Reuben",
            "verse": "Gen. 49:3-4"
        },
        {
            "number": 25,
            "question": "What are the names of the rivers that flow into the Garden of Eden?",
            "options": ["Nile, Jordan River, and The Dead Sea", "Pison, Gihon, Hiddekel and Euphrates", "Pacific, Atlantic, and Victor", "Volta, Cavala, Lofa and Mano"],
            "answer": "Pison, Gihon, Hiddekel and Euphrates",
            "verse": "Gen. 2:11-14"
        },
        {
            "number": 26,
            "question": "How many were the daughters of Philip who are virgins and prophetesses?",
            "options": [4, 5, 3, 7],
            "answer": 4,
            "verse": "Acts 21:9"
        },
        {
            "number": 27,
            "question": "Name the three men that were swallowed up by the earth for conspiracy against Moses.",
            "options": ["Bildad, Eliphaz, Zophar", "Korah, Dathan, and Abirah", "Enoch, Ephram, Elijah", "Paul, Salor, Peter"],
            "answer": "Korah, Dathan, and Abirah",
            "verse": " Num. 16:1-34"
        },
        {
            "number": 28,
            "question": "Who is the man that wanted to obtain the gift of the Holy Spirit with money?",
            "options": ["Obededom", "Solomon", "David", "Simeon"],
            "answer": "Simon",
            "verse": "Simon, the sorcerer, Acts 8:18"
        },
        {
            "number": 29,
            "question": "Who is the first Christian Martyr?",
            "options": ["Peter", "Jesus", "Stephen", "Lazarus"],
            "answer": "Stephen",
            "verse": "Acts 7:59-60"
        },
        {
            "number": 30,
            "question": "How long did the Israelites live in Egypt?",
            "options": [400, 430, 40, 7],
            "answer": 430,
            "verse": "430 yrs, Exo. 12:40"
        },
        {
            "number": 31,
            "question": "Who offered strange fire before the Lord and were struck dead?",
            "options": ["Nadab and Abihu", "Hophni and Phinehas", "Joshua and Caleb", "Joseph and Moses"],
            "answer": "Nadab and Abihu",
            "verse": "Nadab and Abihu, the sons of Aaron, Lev. 10:1"
        },
        {
            "number": 32,
            "question": "Which person became lame as a result of a fall from a fleeing nurse?",
            "options": ["James", "Sherma", "Eleazer", "Melphibosheth"],
            "answer": "Melphibosheth",
            "verse": "2Sam. 4:4"
        },
        {
            "number": 33,
            "question": "Who were the two men who ate books?",
            "options": ["Moses and Melchizedek", "John and Ezekiel", "Peter and Paul", "Jesus and John"],
            "answer": "John and Ezekiel",
            "verse": "John Rev.10:9 and Ezekiel Ezek. 2:8-9"
        },
        {
            "number": 34,
            "question": "How old was Moses when he died?",
            "options": ["120 yrs", "127 yrs", "100 yrs", "75 yrs"],
            "answer": "120 yrs",
            "verse": "Deut. 34:7"
        },
        {
            "number": 35,
            "question": "Which man's rash vow cursed his daughter's death?",
            "options": ["Shem", "Ham", "Jephthah", "Eliphaz"],
            "answer": "Jephthah",
            "verse": "Judges 11:30-40"
        },
        {
            "number": 36,
            "question": "Who was the first cattle rearer on earth?",
            "options": ["Cain", "Abel", "Seth", "Jabel"],
            "answer": "Jabel",
            "verse": "Gen. 4:20"
        },
        {
            "number": 37,
            "question": "What is the name of the place that had a widow whose only son died and was restored to life by Jesus?",
            "options": ["The Nazarite woman", "the widow of Nian", "The Samaritain woman", "Syrophoenician woman"],
            "answer": "The widow of Nain",
            "verse": "Luke 7:11-16"
        },
        {
            "number": 38,
            "question": "Name the king whose hand got withered.",
            "options": ["David", "Amaziah", "Ahaziah", "Jeroboam"],
            "answer": "Jeroboam",
            "verse": "1Kings 13:4"
        },
        {
            "number": 39,
            "question": "Which place was Abraham and Sarah buried?",
            "options": ["In Egypt", "In the cave of Malcphelah", "In the valley in the land of Moah. Sepulchre unknown", "On mount Ararat"],
            "answer": "In the cave of Machpelah",
            "verse": "In the cave of Machpelah in the field of Ephron. Gen. 25:9-10, 23:19"
        },
        {
            "number": 40,
            "question": "What is the meaning of Hosea daughter's name Lo-ruhammah?",
            "options": ["The glory has departed from Israel", "God has withdrawn his mercy from Israel(Rejection)", "The beauty of the world", "Israel pride"],
            "answer": "God has withdrawn his mercy from Israel(Rejection)",
            "verse": "Hosea 1:6"
        },
        {
            "number": 41,
            "question": "What were the food of John the Baptist in the desert?",
            "options": ["Bake Cake and Water", "Locust and Wild honey", "Quaiis and Manna", "The dove brought bread"],
            "answer": "Locust and wild honey",
            "verse": "Matt. 3:4"
        },
        {
            "number": 42,
            "question": "List the gifts given to Jesus by the wise men.",
            "options": ["Gold, frankincense, and myrrh", "Goat, Cow and Sheep", "Clothes and Money", "Olive oil, anointing oil, and kanji"],
            "answer": "Gold, frankincense, and myrrh",
            "verse": "Matt. 2:11"
        },
        {
            "number": 43,
            "question": "How many baskets of fishes were left when Jesus fed the five thousand(5,000) men with five(5) loaves of bread and two fishes?",
            "options": [12, 5, 2, 7],
            "answer": 12,
            "verse": "Twelve(12) baskets, Luke 9:17"
        },
        {
            "number": 44,
            "question": "What is the name of the family that never took wine nor built houses throughout their generation because of the initial command by their father?",
            "options": ["Nadab", "Abihu", "Rechabites", "Jonadab"],
            "answer": "Rechabites",
            "verse": "Rechabites, their father name was Jonadab the son of Rechab. Jeremiah 35:17"
        },
        {
            "number": 45,
            "question": "Which prophet is referred to as the weeping prophet?",
            "options": ["Elijah", "Elisha", "Ezekiel", "Jeremiah"],
            "answer": "Jeremiah",
            "verse": "Prophet Jeremiah"
        },
        {
            "number": 46,
            "question": "Who were the two sons of King Sennacherib that killed he while hes was worshiping his god?",
            "options": ["Sharezer and Adrammelech", "Eliphaz and Zophar", "Joshua and Caleb", "Hophni and Phinehas"],
            "answer": "Sharezer and Adrammelech",
            "verse": "2Kings 19:32-36"
        },
        {
            "number": 47,
            "question": "How many prophets of Baal were slain by Elijah when God answered by fire?",
            "options": [430, 1000, 450, 150],
            "answer": 450,
            "verse": "450 prophets, 1Kings 18:19-40"
        },
        {
            "number": 48,
            "question": "What is the name of the wife of Moses?",
            "options": ["Sarah", "Rebekah", "Asenath", "Zipporah"],
            "answer": "Zipporah",
            "verse": "Exo. 18:2"
        },
        {
            "number": 49,
            "question": "How long did Jesus stay on earth after His resurrection?",
            "options": ["3 days", "40 days", "12 days", "3 yrs"],
            "answer": "40 days",
            "verse": "Acts 1:3"
        },
        {
            "number": 50,
            "question": "What is the name of Solomon's mother?",
            "options": ["Michal", "Abigail", "Bathsheba", "Asenath"],
            "answer": "Bathsheba",
            "verse": "Bathsheba (Uriah's wife), 2Sam. 12:24"
        },
        {
            "number": 51,
            "question": "State the royal rule.",
            "options": ["Love youself as you wish", "Therefore all things whatsoever ye would that men should do to you: do ye even so to them: for this is the law and the prophets", "Thy shall love thine neighbor as thyself", "Thy shall not steal"],
            "answer": "Thou shall love thy neighbor as thyself",
            "verse": "James 2:8"
        },
        {
            "number": 52,
            "question": "How many of the disciples were in the upper room in the day of Pentecost when the Holy Ghost came down?",
            "options": [120, 12, 500, 3],
            "answer": 120,
            "verse": "Acts 1:13-15, 2:1"
        },
        {
            "number": 53,
            "question": "At the feeding of four thousand (4,000) men by Jesus with seven full baskets left, how many loaves of bread and fishes were used?",
            "options": ["3 loaves and few fishes", "7 loaves and few fishes", "7 loaves and 4 fishes", "10 loaves and 7 fishes"],
            "answer": "7 loaves and few fishes",
            "verse": "Seven(7) loaves and few fishes. Matt: 15:36-37"
        },
        {
            "number": 54,
            "question": "Of the seven churches listed in the book of Revelation, which church is the loyal or best church?",
            "options": ["Laodicea", "Philadelphia", "Thyatira", "Sardis"],
            "answer": "Philadelphia",
            "verse": "The church in Philadelphia. Rev. 3:7-13"
        },
        {
            "number": 55,
            "question": "How many sons of Ahab in Samaria were killed by Jehu?",
            "options": [700, 70, 70000, 7],
            "answer": 70,
            "verse": "Seventy(70) 2Kings 10:1-7"
        },
        {
            "number": 56,
            "question": "What is the number of souls saved in the flood of Noah?",
            "options": [4, 5, 7, 8],
            "answer": 8,
            "verse": "8 souls. Gen. 7:13"
        },
        {
            "number": 57,
            "question": "Which king out of pride went to burn incense in the temple and was stricken with leprosy?",
            "options": ["Uriah", "Sennacherib", "Uzziah", "Uzzah"],
            "answer": "Uzziah",
            "verse": "2 Chro. 26:16-21"
        },
        {
            "number": 58,
            "question": "Name the three men that conspired against Nehemiah to hinder the building of the wall.",
            "options": ["Shadrach, Meshach, Abednego", "Sanballat, Tobiah, Geshen", "Sharezer, Adrammelech, Sennacherib", "Bildad, Eliphaz, Zophar"],
            "answer": "Sanballat, Tobiah, Geshen",
            "verse": "Nehemiah 6"
        },
        {
            "number": 59,
            "question": "How long did Moses stay on Mount Sinai with god?",
            "options": ["3 days and nights", "40 days and nights", "30 days and nights", "7 days and nights"],
            "answer": "40 days and nights",
            "verse": "Exo. 24:18"
        },
        {
            "number": 60,
            "question": "Who bears the name Edom?",
            "options": ["Edomite", "Esau", "Paul", "Saul"],
            "answer": "Esau",
            "verse": "Gen. 36:1"
        },
        {
            "number": 61,
            "question": "What is the sign given to King Hezekiah that God has added extra 15 years to his life span?",
            "options": ["The sun dial returned 10 degrees backward", "The sun stood still and the moon stayed", "The riven brought a dry leave", "There was no rain for 3 years"],
            "answer": "The sun dial returned 10 degrees backward",
            "verse": "Isaiah 38:5-8"
        },
        {
            "number": 62,
            "question": "What are the names of the two sons of Eli?",
            "options": ["Joshua and Caleb", "Moses and Aaron", "Cain and Abel", "Hophni and Phinehas"],
            "answer": "Hophni and Phinehas",
            "verse": "1 Sam. 4:17"
        },
        {
            "number": 63,
            "question": "What is the name of the second wife of Abraham?",
            "options": ["Hagai", "Sarah", "Ketura", "Rebekah"],
            "answer": "Keturah",
            "verse": "Gen. 25:1"
        },
        {
            "number": 64,
            "question": "Who did the Bible refer to as a mighty hunter before the Lord?",
            "options": ["Gideon", "Nimrod", "Goliah", "Esau"],
            "answer": "Nimrod",
            "verse": "Gen. 10:9"
        },
        {
            "number": 65,
            "question": "Who saw the nakedness of his father and broadcasted it to his brethren instead of covering it?",
            "options": ["Ham", "Absalom", "Reuben", "Judah"],
            "answer": "Ham",
            "verse": "Ham, the father of Canaan. Gen. 9:21"
        },
        {
            "number": 66,
            "question": "Who was the first high priest of Israel?",
            "options": ["Melchizedek", "Aaron", "Jesus", "Moses"],
            "answer": "Aaron",
            "verse": "Num. 3:3"
        },
        {
            "number": 67,
            "question": "What is Esther's Jewish name?",
            "options": ["Bathsheba", "Haddassah", "Asenath", "Holy Mary"],
            "answer": "Hadassah",
            "verse": "Esther 2:7"
        },
        {
            "number": 68,
            "question": "Who was the three Jews who did not bow to the golden image of King Nebuchadnezzar?",
            "options": ["Shadrach, Meshach, Abednego", "Sanballat, Tobiah, Geshen", "Bildad, Eliphaz, Zophar", "Enoch, Ephram, Elijah"],
            "answer": "Shadrach, Meshach, Abednego",
            "verse": "Dan. 3:14"
        },
        {
            "number": 69,
            "question": "How old was Abraham when he gave birth to Isaac?",
            "options": ["40 yrs", "75 yrs", "85 yrs", "100 yrs"],
            "answer": "100 yrs",
            "verse": "Gen. 21:5"
        },
        {
            "number": 70,
            "question": "How much was Joseph sold for to the Ismaelites?",
            "options": ["20 pieces of silver", "30 pieces of silver", "40 pieces of silver", "25 pieces of silver"],
            "answer": "20 pieces of silver",
            "verse": "Gen. 37:28"
        },
        {
            "number": 71,
            "question": "Judah's first son, Er, was wicked such that God slew him. How do you refer to his brother who went into his wife but spilled it on the ground least he should give seed to his brother?",
            "options": ["Dan", "Onan", "Chain", "Ham"],
            "answer": "Onan",
            "verse": "Gen. 38:9"
        },
        {
            "number": 72,
            "question": "How many years did Jacob live in the land of Egypt?",
            "options": [20, 17, 18, 40],
            "answer": 17,
            "verse": "Gen. 47:28"
        },
        {
            "number": 73,
            "question": "Where did Moses smite the rock and water rushed ourt when Israelites murmured against God?",
            "options": ["Mount Sinai", "The Red Sea", "Rephidim", "In the desert"],
            "answer": "Rephidim",
            "verse": "Exo. 17:1"
        },
        {
            "number": 74,
            "question": "What is the names of the man whom the Bible referred to as an eloquent man and mighty in scriptures?",
            "options": ["Paul", "Timothy", "Apollos", "Solomon"],
            "answer": "Apollos",
            "verse": "Acts 18:24"
        },
        {
            "number": 75,
            "question": "What are the names of the persons that contested for the position of Juda Ischariot?",
            "options": ["Salor and Paul", "Joseph and Moses", "Joseph and Mathias", "Cain and Abel"],
            "answer": "Joseph and Mathias",
            "verse": "Joseph called Barsabas and Mathias. Acts 1:23"
        },
        {
            "number": 76,
            "question": "Where did God tell Abraham to go and offer Isaac as a scarifice?",
            "options": ["Land of Judah", "At Jacob's well", "Land of Moriah", "Mount Sinai"],
            "answer": "Land of Moriah",
            "verse": "Gen. 22:2"
        },
        {
            "number": 77,
            "question": "What are the names of the husband and wife who were strucked dead by the Holy Ghost because they sold a possession and lied that they brought all?",
            "options": ["Hannah and Ekannah", "Lot and his wife", "Annias and Sapphira", "Uriah and Bethshebath"],
            "answer": "Annias and Sapphira",
            "verse": "Acts 5:1-10"
        },
        {
            "number": 78,
            "question": "Give the name of the two men who Moses chose to lead every oher wisehearted man in Israel to build the tabernacle for the congregation.",
            "options": ["Meshach and Abednego", "Tobiah and Geshen", "Bezalel and Aholiah", "Eliphaz and Zophar"],
            "answer": "Bezalel and Aholiah",
            "verse": "Exo. 36:1"
        },
        {
            "number": 79,
            "question": "Twelve men were sent to spy the land of Canaan. Ten came back with an evil report. Name the two spies who brought a good report that pleased the Lord.",
            "options": ["Cain and Abel", "Joshua and Caleb", "Hophni and Phinehas", "Jacob and Esau"],
            "answer": "Joshua and Caleb",
            "verse": "Num.14:6"
        },
        {
            "number": 80,
            "question": "Who stole the accused thing that led to the defeat of the Israelite by the people of Ai?",
            "options": ["Uzzah", "Judah", "Cain", "Achan"],
            "answer": "Achan",
            "verse": "Joshua 7:1-2"
        },
        {
            "number": 81,
            "question": "What miracle took place when God fought for Israel againg the Amorite, under the command of Joshua?",
            "options": ["The sun dial returned 10 degrees backward", "The sun stood still and the moon stayed", "The sky became dark for three days", "The pillar of fire by night and the pillar of cloud by day"],
            "answer": "The sun stood still and the moon stayed",
            "verse": "Joshua. 10:12"
        },
        {
            "number": 82,
            "question": "How many people did God tell Elijah that have not bowed to the god of Baal contrary to Elijah's misconception as the prophet of God left?",
            "options": [7000, 70, 70000, 7],
            "answer": 7000,
            "verse": "1 King 19:18"
        },
        {
            "number": 83,
            "question": "Who is the king of Israel that did what was right in the sight of God but not with a perfect heart?",
            "options": ["Amaziah", "Joash", "Ketura", "Jeroboam"],
            "answer": "Amaziah",
            "verse": "2 Chro. 25:2"
        },
        {
            "number": 84,
            "question": "What is the name of the man who counselled Absalom to lie with all his father's concunbines before Israel?",
            "options": ["Ahithophel", "Amnan", "Goliah", "Esau"],
            "answer": "Ahithophel",
            "verse": "2 Sam. 16:21"
        },
        {
            "number": 85,
            "question": "When satan stood against Israel and provoked David to number Israel, how many people were slain by the Lord?",
            "options": [7000, 70000, 3050, 144000],
            "answer": 70000,
            "verse": "1 Chro. 21:14"
        },
        {
            "number": 86,
            "question": "'Nay; but i will verily buy it for the full price; for I will not take that which is thine for the Lord nor offer offerings without cost.' Who said it and to whom?",
            "options": ["Melchizedek to Abraham", "Abraham to Adrammelech", "Jacob to Leban", "David to Ormnn"],
            "answer": "David to Ormnn",
            "verse": "1 Chro. 21:24"
        },
        {
            "number": 87,
            "question": "What is the king with the longest reign in the Bible",
            "options": ["David", "Manasseh", "Saul", "Solomon"],
            "answer": "Manasseh",
            "verse": "Manasseh, 55 years. 2 Kings 21:1"
        },
        {
            "number": 88,
            "question": "In which place were the disciples first called christian?",
            "options": ["Athens", "Antioch", "Greece", "Nazarite"],
            "answer": "Antioch",
            "verse": "Acts 11:26"
        },
        {
            "number": 89,
            "question": "what are the names of Lazarus's two sisters?",
            "options": ["Elizabeth and Mary", "Hannah and Sarah", "Mary and Martha", "Ruth and Naomi"],
            "answer": "Mary and Martha",
            "verse": "John 11:1"
        },
        {
            "number": 90,
            "question": "Which king took Judah into Captivity?",
            "options": ["Nebuchadnezzar", "Saul", "Darius", "solomon"],
            "answer": "Nebuchadnezzar",
            "verse": "2 Kings 24. 37:28"
        },
        {
            "number": 91,
            "question": "Who did the angel of the Lord refer to as a mighty man of valor?",
            "options": ["Gideon", "Nimord", "Chain", "Ham"],
            "answer": "Gideon",
            "verse": "Judges 6:312"
        },
        {
            "number": 92,
            "question": "Who is the woman whose daughter Jesus cast out the unclean spirit?",
            "options": ["Syrophoenician woman", "the widow of Nian", "The Samaritain woman", "The Nazarite woman"],
            "answer": "Syrophoenician woman",
            "verse": "Mark. 7:24-30"
        },
        {
            "number": 93,
            "question": "Where did David first reign as king?",
            "options": ["Judah", "Egypt", "Jerusalem", "Hebron"],
            "answer": "Hebron",
            "verse": "2 Sam. 2:1-4"
        },
        {
            "number": 94,
            "question": "What are the names of the sons of Lot born unto him by his two daughters?",
            "options": ["Moab and Ben-ammi", "Hophni and Phinehas", "Joshua and Caleb", "Jacob and Esau"],
            "answer": "Moab and Ben-ammi",
            "verse": "Gen. 19:6-38"
        },
        {
            "number": 95,
            "question": "How many times was Naaman told by Elijah to dip himself in the Jordan river to receive healing from leprosy?",
            "options": [70, 7, 4, 3],
            "answer": 7,
            "verse": "2 Kings 5:10"
        },
        {
            "number": 96,
            "question": "Who is the queen that was removed and replaced by Esther because she refused to display her beauty before the royal guest",
            "options": ["Elizabeth", "Queen of Egypt", "Vashti", "Naomi"],
            "answer": "Vashti",
            "verse": "1Esther 1:19"
        },
        {
            "number": 97,
            "question": "List the plagues that God sent upon Egypt before Pharaoh allowed Israel go.",
            "options": ["frogs, murrian, lice, flies, locust, boils, darkness", "frogs, flies, lice, locust, darkness, thunder and hails, Nile turn to blood, boils, murrian, death of all the first born", "Nile turn to blood, lice, frogs, flies, locust, row turn to snake", "Heavy rain, Moses killing an egyptian, boils, frogs, flies, lice"],
            "answer": "frogs, flies, lice, locust, darkness, thunder and hails, Nile turn to blood, boils, murrian, death of all the first born",
            "verse": "'frogs Exo. 8:6', 'flies Exo. 8:24', 'lice Exo. 8:18', 'locust Exo. 10:13', 'darkness Exo. 10:22-23', 'thunder and hail Exo. 9:23', 'Nile turn to blood Exo. 7:20', 'boils Exo. 9:10', 'murrian Exo. 9:6', 'death of all the first born Exo. 12:29'"
        },
        {
            "number": 98,
            "question": "What is the name of the prophet that rebuked David for killing Uriah and taking his wife?",
            "options": ["Samuel", "Nathan", "Elisha", "Elijah"],
            "answer": "Nathan",
            "verse": "2 Sam. 12:7-12"
        },
        {
            "number": 99,
            "question": "With what did God feed the Israelites in the wilderness?",
            "options": ["Quaiis and Manna", "Locust and Wild honey", "Bake Cake and Water", "Bread of life"],
            "answer": "Quaiis and Manna",
            "verse": "Exo. 16:13-15"
        },
        {
            "number": 100,
            "question": "Who delivered Solomon from Adonijah's plot of taking even the throne of David?",
            "options": ["King David", "Joab", "Prophet Nathan", "Prophet Samuel"],
            "answer": "Prophet Nathan",
            "verse": "1 Kings 1:11-39"
        },
        {
            "number": 101,
            "question": "List the three temptations that Satan brought before Jesus in the wilderness.",
            "options": ["That Jesus should turn stone to bread, That Jesus should turn water to wine, That Jesus should worship him(Satan)", "That Jesus should throw himself down from the pinnacle of the temple harmless, That Jesus should turn water to wine, That Jesus should worship him(Satan)", "That Jesus should worship him(Satan), That Jesus should turn stone to bread, That Jesus should die for mankind's sin", "That Jesus should throw himself down from the pinnacle of the temple harmless, That Jesus should turn water to wine, That Jesus should worship him(Satan)", "That Jesus should worship him(Satan), That Jesus should turn stone to bread,That Jesus should throw himself down from the pinnacle of the temple harmless"],
            "answer": "That Jesus should worship him(Satan), That Jesus should turn stone to bread,That Jesus should throw himself down from the pinnacle of the temple harmless",
            "verse": "Matt. 4:9"
        },
        {
            "number": 102,
            "question": "What was the sins of the daughters of Lot?",
            "options": ["They made him drunk", "They insulted him", "They killed their mother and married their father", "They got their father drunk and made him lie with them"],
            "answer": "They got their father drunk and made him lie with them",
            "verse": "Gen. 19:30-36"
        },
        {
            "number": 103,
            "question": "Which place was the camp site for the Israelites in Egypt?",
            "options": ["Gogotta", "Goshen", "Nachon's threshing floor", "Rephidim"],
            "answer": "Goshen",
            "verse": "Gen. 45:9-10"
        },
        {
            "number": 104,
            "question": "State the number of kings that ruled united Israel.",
            "options": [3, 4, 2, 5],
            "answer": 3,
            "verse": "King Saul (1 Sam. 10:1), King David (2 Sam. 2:1-4), and King Solomon (1 Kings 1:39)"
        },
        {
            "number": 105,
            "question": "How old was Sarah when she died?",
            "options": ["27 yrs", "100 yrs", "99 yrs", "127 years"],
            "answer": "127 yrs",
            "verse": "Gen. 23:1"
        },
        {
            "number": 106,
            "question": "Name the two brothers of Abraham.",
            "options": ["Joseph and Mathias", "Moses and Aaron", "Nahor and Haran", "Cain and Abel"],
            "answer": "Nahor and Haran",
            "verse": "Gen. 11:27"
        },
        {
            "number": 107,
            "question": "Where did  God create different languages",
            "options": ["Egypt", "In the desert", "On the day of pentecost", "At the tower of barbel"],
            "answer": "At the tower of barbel",
            "verse": "Gen. 11:1-9"
        },
        {
            "number": 108,
            "question": "Who healed Eneas that has been crippled for the past eight years at Lydda?",
            "options": ["John", "Peter", "Paul", "Matthew"],
            "answer": "Peter",
            "verse": "Acts 9:33-34"
        },
        {
            "number": 109,
            "question": "Where did Jacob sleep when he dreamt and saw an angel descending and ascending in a ladder from heaven to earth",
            "options": ["Jacob's Well", "Bethlehem", "Bethel", "Egypt"],
            "answer": "Bethel",
            "verse": "Bethel, Old name of Luz Gen. 28:10-19"
        },
        {
            "number": 110,
            "question": "Where did the Israelites find twelve fountains of water and seventy palm trees during the wilderness journey?",
            "options": ["Edom", "Elim", "Goshen", "Rephidim"],
            "answer": "Elim",
            "verse": "Num. 33:9-24"
        },
        {
            "number": 111,
            "question": "Who is referred to as scribe of the words of the commandments of the law of the God of heaven?",
            "options": ["Apollos", "Ezra", "Paul", "David"],
            "answer": "Ezra",
            "verse": "Ezra 7:12"
        },
        {
            "number": 112,
            "question": "What is the meaning of Ichabod?",
            "options": ["God has withdrawn his mercy from Israel(Rejection)", "The glory has departed from Israel", "The fallen wall of Jerico", "The Lord will proivde"],
            "answer": "The glory has departed from Israel",
            "verse": "1 Sam. 4:21"
        },
        {
            "number": 113,
            "question": "Name the man that prayed that the sun and the moon should stay a day longer which manifested?",
            "options": ["Gideon", "David", "Hezekiah", "Joshua"],
            "answer": "Joshua",
            "verse": "Josh. 10:12-14"
        },
        {
            "number": 114,
            "question": "Give the name of Moses' sister?",
            "options": ["Sarah", "Zipporah", "Miriam", "Esther"],
            "answer": "Miriam",
            "verse": "Num. 26:59"
        },
        {
            "number": 115,
            "question": "Which of David's wife was barren for life?",
            "options": ["Michal", "Bathsheba", "Abigail", "Miriam"],
            "answer": "Michal",
            "verse": "Michal, Saul's daughter. 2 Sam. 6:23"
        },
        {
            "number": 116,
            "question": "Where was Uzzah struck dead for touching the Ark of God?",
            "options": ["Nachon's threshing floor", "Gogotta", "Goshen", "Rephidim"],
            "answer": "Nachon's threshing floor",
            "verse": "2 Sam. 6:23"
        },
        {
            "number": 117,
            "question": "What is the name of the mother of Timothy?",
            "options": ["Elizabeth", "Eunice", "Asenath", "Holy Mary"],
            "answer": "Eunice",
            "verse": "2 Tim. 1:5"
        },
        {
            "number": 118,
            "question": "How many years did the Israelites wander in the wilderness?",
            "options": [12, 30, 40, 70],
            "answer": 40,
            "verse": "40 years, Num. 14:33"
        },
        {
            "number": 119,
            "question": "Who is the child before his conception that the father was told that no razor should touch his hair and must never take in strong drink?",
            "options": ["John the baptist", "Peter", "Solomon", "Samson"],
            "answer": "Samson",
            "verse": "Judges 13:2-25"
        },
        {
            "number": 120,
            "question": "Where did Aaron died?",
            "options": ["Mount Sinai", "Mount Ararat", "Mount Olive", "Mount Hur"],
            "answer": "Mount Hur",
            "verse": "Num. 20:27-28"
        },
        {
            "number": 121,
            "question": "Who is the similititude of Christ in the Old Testament?",
            "options": ["Adam", "Abraham", "Melchizedek", "Angel"],
            "answer": "Melchizedek",
            "verse": "Heb. 6:20"
        },
        {
            "number": 122,
            "question": "Which of the disciples' mother-in-law did Jesus heal of fever?",
            "options": ["Matthew", "John", "Andrew", "Peter"],
            "answer": "Peter",
            "verse": "Mark. 1:30-31"
        },
        {
            "number": 123,
            "question": "What is the name of Moses' father-in-law?",
            "options": ["Leban", "Jethro", "Pharaoh", "Ephraim"],
            "answer": "Jethro",
            "verse": "Exo. 4:18"
        },
        {
            "number": 124,
            "question": "Name the seven(7) deacons selected to oversee the affairs of the early church.",
            "options": ["Paul, Andrew, Philip, Nicolas, Timon, Nicanor", "Nicanor, Nicolas, Parmenas, Philip, Prochorus, Stephen, Timon", "Apollos, Solomon, James, Andrew, Peter, Philip, Timothy", "Aaron, Nicanor, Nicolas, Parmenas, Philip, Prochorus, Stephen, Timon"],
            "answer": "Nicanor, Nicolas, Parmenas, Philip, Prochorus, Stephen, Timon",
            "verse": "Acts 6:5"
        },
        {
            "number": 125,
            "question": "What is the name of Adonijah's mother?",
            "options": ["Bathsheba", "Michal", "Abigail", "Haggith"],
            "answer": "Haggith",
            "verse": "Haggaith (One of David's wives 2 Sam. 3:4)"
        },
        {
            "number": 126,
            "question": "Who healed the man at the beautiful gate?",
            "options": ["John", "Paul", "Peter", "Elijah"],
            "answer": "Peter",
            "verse": "Acts 3:6"
        },
        {
            "number": 127,
            "question": "What is the name of the king that captured 70 kings and cut off their great toes and thumbs?",
            "options": ["Amaziah", "Jeroboam", "Adoni-bezek", "Ahaziah"],
            "answer": "Adoni-bezek",
            "verse": "Judges 1:7"
        },
        {
            "number": 128,
            "question": "What is the number of men(Army) that Gideon used to defeat the midianites?",
            "options": [700, 7000, 300, 3000],
            "answer": 300,
            "verse": "Judges 7:7"
        },
        {
            "number": 129,
            "question": "Who was Samson's wife that betrayed him?",
            "options": ["Docas", "Delilah", "Haggai", "Jazabel"],
            "answer": "Delilah",
            "verse": "Judges 16:18"
        },
        {
            "number": 130,
            "question": "What is the total number of judges that Israel had?",
            "options": [12, 5, 10, 15],
            "answer": 15,
            "verse": "15 Judges. They were: Othniel Judg. 3:9, Ehud Judg. 3:15, Shamgar Judg. 3:31, Deborah Judg. 4:5, Gideon Judg. 6:36, Abimelech Judg. 9:1, Tola Judg. 10:1, Jair Judg. 10:3, Jephthah Judg. 11:11, Ibzan Judg. 12:8, Elon Judg. 12:11, Abdon Judg. 12:13, Samson Judg. 16:30, Eli 1Sam. 4:18, Samuel 1Sam. 7:15"
        },
        {
            "number": 131,
            "question": "What are the names of the two handmaid of Jacob's two wives?",
            "options": ["Ruth and Naomi", "Mary and Martha", "Deborah and Delilah", "Bilhah, Zipah"],
            "answer": "Bilhah, Zipah",
            "verse": "Bilhah - Rachel's handmaid, Zipah - Leah's handmaid, Gen. 35:25-26"

        },
        {
            "number": 132,
            "question": "How old was David when he started to reign over Israel and how many years did he reign?",
            "options": ["40 yrs old, reigned 30 yrs", "30 yrs old, reigned 40 yrs", "20 yrs old, reigned 30 yrs", "30 yrs old, reigned 20 yrs"],
            "answer": "30 yrs old, reigned 40 yrs",
            "verse": "2 Sam. 5:4"
        },
        {
            "number": 133,
            "question": "Whose bones in his grave revived a dead man?",
            "options": ["Elijah", "Elisha", "Abraham", "Moses"],
            "answer": "Elisha",
            "verse": "2 Kings 13:21"
        },
        {
            "number": 134,
            "question": "Which of the disciples raised Tabitha(Dorcas) back to life?",
            "options": ["Paul", "Peter", "John", "Stephen"],
            "answer": "Peter",
            "verse": "Acts 9:36-41"
        },
        {
            "number": 135,
            "question": "Who finally took the position of Judas Iscariot after he betrayed Jesus?",
            "options": ["Stephen", "Paul", "Joseph", "Mathias"],
            "answer": "Mathias",
            "verse": "Acts 1:26"
        },
        {
            "number": 136,
            "question": "What is the name of the place where Jesus was crucified?",
            "options": ["Mount Ararat", "Mount Sinai", "Golgotha", "Mount Olive"],
            "answer": "Golgotha",
            "verse": "Matt. 27:33"
        },
        {
            "number": 137,
            "question": "Name the man that lost a crown?",
            "options": ["Reuben", "Saul", "David", "Adonijah"],
            "answer": "Saul",
            "verse": "1 Sam. 15:26-28"
        },
        {
            "number": 138,
            "question": "Who healed the crippled at Lystra?",
            "options": ["Stephen", "Paul", "Joseph", "Mathias"],
            "answer": "Paul",
            "verse": "Acts 14:8-10"
        },
        {
            "number": 139,
            "question": "How many tribes make up Israel under the reign of Jeroboam? (Northern Israel)",
            "options": [3, 10, 7, 20],
            "answer": 10,
            "verse": "10 tribes 1 Kings 11:31"
        },
        {
            "number": 140,
            "question": "Who was referred to as the king of Salem in the old testament?",
            "options": ["Abraham", "Adrammelech", "Sennacherib", "Melchizedek"],
            "answer": "Melchizedek",
            "verse": "Gen. 14:18"
        },
        {
            "number": 141,
            "question": "Which place was Philip when he was caught off and where was he found?",
            "options": ["Caught away from Gaza and foound the city of Azotus", "Caught away from Nazareth and foound the city of Jerusalem", "Caught away from Babylon and foound the city of Damacus", "Caught away from Egypt and foound the city of Israel"],
            "answer": "Caught away from Gaza and foound the city of Azotus",
            "verse": "Acts 8:26, 39-40"

        },
        {
            "number": 142,
            "question": "Who was described in the Bible as the most handsome and has long hair that wweighed two hundred shekels?",
            "options": ["Absalom", "Adonijah", "Solomon", "Ahithophel"],
            "answer": "Absalom",
            "verse": "2 Sam. 14:25-26"
        },
        {
            "number": 143,
            "question": "With what instrument did David use to kill Goliath?",
            "options": ["A Sling with a stone", "A bowl and arrow", "A gun", "A knife"],
            "answer": "A Sling with a stone",
            "verse": "1 Sam. 17:49-50"
        },
        {
            "number": 144,
            "question": "What is the name of the daughter of Leah whom Schechem the son of Harmor defiled that led to a tribal war?",
            "options": ["Michal", "Dinah", "Jazabel", "Haggai"],
            "answer": "Dinah",
            "verse": "Gen. 34:1-29"
        },
        {
            "number": 145,
            "question": "Who struct the Syrian army with blindness when they came to arrest him?",
            "options": ["Elijah", "Enoch", "Joseph", "Elisha"],
            "answer": "Elisha",
            "verse": "Prophet Elisha 2 Kings 6:18"
        },
        {
            "number": 146,
            "question": "Name the man that was swallowed by a fish and was in it belly for three(3) days before he was vomited out?",
            "options": ["Noah", "Abraham", "Jonah", "Moses"],
            "answer": "Jonah",
            "verse": "Jonah 1:17"
        },
        {
            "number": 147,
            "question": "Who are the parents of Samuel?",
            "options": ["Sarah and Abraham", "Rebekah and Isaac", "Elkanah and Hannah", "Mary and Joseph"],
            "answer": "Elkanah and Hannah",
            "verse": "1 Sam. 1:20-23"
        },
        {
            "number": 148,
            "question": "Give the name of the man referred to as \"a man after God's heart\"?",
            "options": ["Abraham", "David", "Joseph", "Job"],
            "answer": "David",
            "verse": "1 Sam. 13:13-14"
        },
        {
            "number": 149,
            "question": "What is the name of the wife of Nabai, the rich man in Maon that David married?",
            "options": ["Sarah", "Michal", "Abigail", "Dinah"],
            "answer": "Abigail",
            "verse": "1 Sam. 25:39"
        },
        {
            "number": 150,
            "question": "Name the prophet that caused and axe into the water to float by just casting a stick into the water?",
            "options": ["Elijah", "Enoch", "Samuel", "Elisha"],
            "answer": "Elisha",
            "verse": "2 Kings 6:5-6"
        },
        {
            "number": 151,
            "question": "Who was struck with blindness by Paul's prayer for trying to turn the deputy of the country(Paphos) by name Sergius Paulus from the faith?",
            "options": ["Bar~Jesus(Elymas)", "Simeon", "Shimei", "Ahithophel"],
            "answer": "Bar~Jesus(Elymas)",
            "verse": "Acts 13:6-11"
        },
        {
            "number": 152,
            "question": "What is the name of man of the house of Saul who cursed David when Absalom rebelled saying, \"Come out, Come out, thou bloody man,  and thou man Belial\"?",
            "options": ["Adonijah", "Simeon", "Shimei", "Ahithophel"],
            "answer": "Shimei",
            "verse": "Shimei, the son of Gera 2 Sam. 16:5"
        },
        {
            "number": 153,
            "question": "Quote the chapter and verse in the Bible for the first messaic promise.",
            "options": ["Matt. 4:4", "Gen. 3:15", "Rev. 17", "Isa. 9:6"],
            "answer": "Gen. 3:15",
            "verse": "Gen. 3:15"
        },
        {
            "number": 154,
            "question": "Who prophesied to dry bones in a vision and they stood upon their feet with flesh, breath entered into them and became a great army?",
            "options": ["John", "Isaiah", "Ezekiel", "Moses"],
            "answer": "Ezekiel",
            "verse": "Ezek. 37:1-10"
        },
        {
            "number": 155,
            "question": "What is the name of the commander of David's army?",
            "options": ["Joab", "Jashobeam", "Joseph", "Eleazer"],
            "answer": "Joab",
            "verse": "2 Sam. 24:2"
        },
        {
            "number": 156,
            "question": "What is the kind of the food brought Elijah by the angel when he flew from Jazebel that sustained him for forty days and forty nights?",
            "options": ["Quaiis and Manna", "Locust and Wild honey", "Bake Cake and Water", "Bread of life"],
            "answer": "Bake Cake and Water",
            "verse": "1 Kings 19:6"
        },
        {
            "number": 157,
            "question": "Which people and by what number were slain by the Lord for looking into the Ark of God?",
            "options": ["Men of Bethlehems, 50,070", "Men of Benjaminites, 70,000", "Men of Judah, 7,000", "Men of Gideon, 300"],
            "answer": "Men of Bethlehems, 50,070",
            "verse": "1 Sam. 6:19"
        },
        {
            "number": 158,
            "question": "Where did the Ark of Noah rest after the flood?",
            "options": ["Mount Sinai", "Mount Ararat", "Mount Hur", "Mount Olive"],
            "answer": "Mount Ararat",
            "verse": "Gen. 8:4"
        },
        {
            "number": 159,
            "question": "What is the name of the man who became leprous due to covertousness?",
            "options": ["Elisha", "Timothy", "Gehazi", "Joab"],
            "answer": "Gehazi",
            "verse": "2 Kings 7:21-27"
        },
        {
            "number": 160,
            "question": "What are the names of the three(3) chief captains of David's army?",
            "options": ["Bildad, Eliphaz, Zophar", "Joab, Jashobeam, Eleazer", "Sanballat, Tobiah, Geshen", "Shadrach, Meshach, Abednego"],
            "answer": "Joab, Jashobeam, Eleazer",
            "verse": "Zeruiah's son Joab, Jashobeam a Hachmonite and Dodo's son Eleazer. 1 Chro. 11:6-12"
        },
        {
            "number": 161,
            "question": "Which of the prophet saw the vision of holy waters?",
            "options": ["Elisha", "Moses", "Elijah", "Ezekiel"],
            "answer": "Ezekiel",
            "verse": "Ezek. 47:1-12"

        },
        {
            "number": 162,
            "question": "What is the name of the man who want to destroy all the Jews and Mordecai but was finally hanged in the gallow he prepared for Mordecai?",
            "options": ["Goliah", "Haman", "Samson", "Ahithophel"],
            "answer": "Haman",
            "verse": "Esther 7:10"
        },
        {
            "number": 163,
            "question": "Which city did Paul find an altar with the inscription \"TO THE UNKNOWN GOD\"?",
            "options": ["Antioch", "Athens", "Nazarite", "Nazarite"],
            "answer": "Athens",
            "verse": "Acts 17:22-23"
        },
        {
            "number": 164,
            "question": "What is the name of the servant of the high priest whom Peter cut off his ear and Jesus restored back when the Jews came to arrest Jesus?",
            "options": ["Juda", "Barbas", "Malchus", "Bartimaeus"],
            "answer": "Malchus",
            "verse": "John 18:10"
        },
        {
            "number": 165,
            "question": "What is the name of the man who cried to God to change his destiny which God granted?",
            "options": ["Abel", "Jabez", "Jabel", "Samson"],
            "answer": "Jabez",
            "verse": "1 Chro. 4:9-10"
        },
        {
            "number": 166,
            "question": "Which king had the shortest reign recorded in the Bible?",
            "options": ["Zimri", "Mannasah", "Joash", "Amaziah"],
            "answer": "Zimri",
            "verse": "King Zimri, 7 days. 1 Kings 16:15"
        },
        {
            "number": 167,
            "question": "How old was Jesus when he began his ministry?",
            "options": ["40 years", "30 years", "45 years", "12 years"],
            "answer": "30 years",
            "verse": "He was 30 years old and lasted only 3 years. Luke 3:23"
        },
        {
            "number": 168,
            "question": "What are the names of the twelve sons of Jacob?",
            "options": ["Joseph, Benjamin, Paul, Andrew, Philip, Nicolas, Timon, Nicanor", "Apollos, Solomon, James, Andrew, Peter, Philip, Timothy", "Reuben, Simeon, Levi, Judah, Issachar, Zebulun, Dan, Naphtali, Gad, Asher, Joseph, Benjamin", "Reuben, Simeon, Levi, Judah, Issachar, Enoch, Ephram, Elijah"],
            "answer": "Reuben, Simeon, Levi, Judah, Issachar, Zebulun, Dan, Naphtali, Gad, Asher, Joseph, Benjamin",
            "verse": "Gen. 35:22-26"
        }
    ],
    "Bible Statistics": [{
            "number": 169,
            "question": "How many parts is the Old Testament divided into?",
            "options": [39, 3, 27, 66],
            "answer": 3,
            "details": "Three(3) parts: The law, the prophets and the writings"
        },
        {
            "number": 170,
            "question": "What is the shortest verse in the Bible?",
            "options": ["Matt. 4:4", "John 11:35", "Esther 5:7", "John 10:30"],
            "answer": "John 11:35",
            "details": "John 11:35"
        },
        {
            "number": 171,
            "question": "What is the shortest chapter in the Bible?",
            "options": ["Jude 1", "3rd John 1", "John 1", "Paslms 117"],
            "answer": "Paslms 117",
            "details": "Paslms 117 - 2 verses"
        },
        {
            "number": 172,
            "question": "How many verses are there in the Bible",
            "options": [5040, 38800, 30542, 22485],
            "answer": 30542,
            "details": "30542 - (22,485 - Old testament and 8,057 New Testament)"
        },
        {
            "number": 173,
            "question": "Name the longest book in the Bible",
            "options": ["John", "Genesis", "Proverbs", "Psalms"],
            "answer": "Psalms",
            "details": "Psalms - 150 Chapter"
        },
        {
            "number": 174,
            "question": "How many books do we have in the Bible?",
            "options": [39, 3, 27, 66],
            "answer": 66,
            "details": "Sixty(66) Book: The New Testament 27, the Old Testament 39"
        },
        {
            "number": 175,
            "question": "Which is the longest book in the New Testament?",
            "options": ["Matthew", "John", "Revelation", "Luke"],
            "answer": "Luke",
            "details": "Luke (24 chapters and 1151 verses)"
        },
        {
            "number": 176,
            "question": "Name the shortest book in the Bible?",
            "options": ["Jude", "2nd John", "Obadiah", "Esther"],
            "answer": "2nd John",
            "details": "2nd John - 13 verses"
        },
        {
            "number": 177,
            "question": "Which is the shortest book in the Bible in the Old Testament?",
            "options": ["Jude", "2nd John", "Obadiah", "Esther"],
            "answer": "Obadiah",
            "details": "Obadiah - (21 verses)"
        },
        {
            "number": 178,
            "question": "Which verse of the Bible is the longest?",
            "options": ["Psalms 119:100", "Esther 8:9", "Rev. 22:10", "Psalms 50:12"],
            "answer": "Esther 8:9",
            "details": "Esther 8:9 - (90 words)"
        },
        {
            "number": 179,
            "question": "Which chapter of the Bible is the longest?",
            "options": ["Psalms 119", "Esther 8", "Rev. 22", "Psalms 50"],
            "answer": "Psalms 119",
            "details": "Psalms - (176 Verses)"
        },
        {
            "number": 180,
            "question": "What is the total number of words in the Bible (KJV)?",
            "options": [30542, 22485, 38800, 845000],
            "answer": 845000,
            "details": "845000 - According to King James Version"
        },
        {
            "number": 181,
            "question": "How many chapters do we have in the Old Testament?",
            "options": [22485, 929, 8057, 1151],
            "answer": 929,
            "details": "929"
        }
    ],
    "Bible Facts": [{
            "number": 182,
            "question": "What is the number of books in the Bible that are referred to as the prophetic books?",
            "options": [17, 18, 27, 66],
            "answer": 18,
            "details": "17 Books of the O.T (5 Major(Isaiah-Daniel), 12 Minor(Hosea-Malachi))\n and 1 book of the N.T(Revelation)"
        },
        {
            "number": 183,
            "question": "Who was the last apostle to die?",
            "options": ["Stephen", "Paul", "John the beloved", "John the baptist"],
            "answer": "John the beloved",
            "details": "John the beloved"
        },
        {
            "number": 184,
            "question": "Name the man that translated the new testament into English before being martyred?",
            "options": ["Stephen", "William Tyndale", "John Wyclif", "Robert Stephen"],
            "answer": "William Tyndale",
            "details": "William Tyndale"
        },
        {
            "number": 185,
            "question": "How many dispensations do we have? Name them",
            "options": [7, 10, 3, 4],
            "answer": 7,
            "details": "Dispensation of innoscence\nAdam and Eve without sin at the garden of Eden \n\nDispensation of Conscience\nAdam and Eve after taken the forbiden fruit\n\nDispensation of Human Govt.\nNoah leadership after the flood\n\nDispensation of law\nMosaic Law at Mt. Sanai\n\nDispensation of Millenium\nPeriod of Christ regin on earth for 1000yrs."
        },
        {
            "number": 186,
            "question": "What are the three oldest manuscripts of the Bible?",
            "options": ["Time New Roman, sans-serif, Helvetica", "Codex Sinaititicus, Codex Alexandrinus, Codex Vaticanus", "serif,  Courier, monospace", "Courier New, Cambria, Cochin"],
            "answer": "Codex Sinaititicus, Codex Alexandrinus, Codex Vaticanus",
            "details": "Codex Sinaititicus, Codex Alexandrinus, Codex Vaticanus"
        },
        {
            "number": 187,
            "question": "How many years did it take to complete the Bible?",
            "options": [40, 1600, 400, 1000],
            "answer": 1600,
            "details": "1600 years"
        },
        {
            "number": 188,
            "question": "How many people wrote the Bible?",
            "options": [66, 40, 39, 20],
            "answer": 40,
            "details": "40 Faithfull men"
        },
        {
            "number": 189,
            "question": "How many books of the Bible are regarded as historical books?",
            "options": [12, 13, 5, 17],
            "answer": 13,
            "details": "13 Books Old Testament(12 Joshua - Esther) and New Testament(1 Acts)"
        },
        {
            "number": 190,
            "question": "How many continents in the world was the Bible written? Name them",
            "options": [3, 7, 12, 4],
            "answer": 3,
            "details": "Three(3) Namely Asia, Africa and Europe"
        },
        {
            "number": 191,
            "question": "Which books of the Bible are referred to as the law book or Pentateuch?",
            "options": ["Gen. - Deut.", "Joshua - Esther", "Job - Lam.", "Isaiah - Daniel"],
            "answer": "Gen. - Deut.",
            "details": "Genesis, Exodus, Leviticus, Numbers, Deuteronomy"
        },
        {
            "number": 192,
            "question": "How many years elasped between Malachi and Matthew?",
            "options": [400, 600, 1000, 30],
            "answer": 400,
            "details": "400 silence period - (Malachi - Last book in Old Testament and Matthew - First book in the New  Testament)"
        },
        {
            "number": 193,
            "question": "In which language was the New Testament written?",
            "options": ["Hebrew", "Greek", "Aramic", "Latin"],
            "answer": "Greek",
            "details": "Greek"
        },
        {
            "number": 194,
            "question": "Which are the books mentioned in the Bible but are not part of the Bible?",
            "options": [
                "Jasher, Nathan, Gad, War of the Lord, Acts of Solomon, The Visions of Iddo the Seer, The Prophecy of Ahijah the Shilonite",
                "Ezekiel, Enoch, Moses, David, Jonah, Noah",
                "John the Baptist, Mathias, Andrew, Philip",
                "Nichodemus, Mathias, Andrew, Jonah, Noah"
            ],
            "answer": "Jasher, Nathan, Gad, War of the Lord, Acts of Solomon, The Visions of Iddo the Seer, The Prophecy of Ahijah the Shilonite",
            "details": "The Book of Jasher - Josh. 10:13\nThe Book of Nathan the prophet\nThe Book of Gad the seer - 1 Chro. 29:29\nThe Book of the War of the Lord -Num. 21:14\nThe book of the Acts of Solomon - 1 Kings 11:41\nThe Visions of Iddo the Seer - 2 Chro. 9:29\nThe Prophecy of Ahijah the Shilonite - 2 Chro. 9:29"
        },
        {
            "number": 195,
            "question": "How many epistles do we have in the New Testament?",
            "options": [21, 27, 39, 66],
            "answer": 21,
            "details": "21 (Romans - Jude)"
        },
        {
            "number": 196,
            "question": "How many books are regarded as poetical?",
            "options": [66, 40, 39, 5],
            "answer": 5,
            "details": "5 Job - Song of Solomon"
        },
        {
            "number": 197,
            "question": "When was the first English Bible completed?",
            "options": [1250, 1380, 1235, 1947],
            "answer": 1380,
            "details": "1380 A.D by John Wyclif"
        },
        {
            "number": 198,
            "question": "Who divided the Bible into verses?",
            "options": ["Stephen", "William Tyndale", "John Wyclif", "Sir Robert Stephen"],
            "answer": "Sir Robert Stephen",
            "details": "Sir Robert Stephen in A.D 115"
        },
        {
            "number": 199,
            "question": "Who divided the Bible into verses?",
            "options": [1250, 1380, 1611, 1947],
            "answer": 1611,
            "details": "1611 in A.D"
        },
        {
            "number": 200,
            "question": "How many times did the word \"God\" appeared in the (K.J.V) Bible?",
            "options": [30542, 22472, 3558, 7736],
            "answer": 3558,
            "details": "3558 times"
        },
        {
            "number": 201,
            "question": "Who first divided the Bible into chapters?",
            "options": ["Sir Cardinal Hugo", "William Tyndale", "John Wyclif", "Sir Robert Stephen"],
            "answer": "Sir Cardinal Hugo",
            "details": "Sir Cardinal Hugo in 1250 A.D"
        },
        {
            "number": 202,
            "question": "The word \"Lord\" appeared how many times in the Bible(K.J.V)?",
            "options": [30542, 7736, 3558, 7736],
            "answer": 7736,
            "details": "7736 times"
        },
        {
            "number": 203,
            "question": "Which books of the Bible are referred to as Canonical books?",
            "options": [
                "Pseudopigrapha books",
                "These are books now in a complete Bible.\nThey are considered as inspired scriprures.",
                "These are books accepted by some sect and rejected by others. Thus they are included in few versions",
                "These are books accepted by some sect and rejected by others."
            ],
            "answer": "These are books now in a complete Bible.\nThey are considered as inspired scriprures.",
            "details": "These are books now in a complete Bible.\nThey are considered as inspired scriprures."
        },
        {
            "number": 204,
            "question": "Which are the books referred to as Apocrypha books?",
            "options": [
                "Pseudopigrapha books",
                "These are books now in a complete Bible.\nThey are considered as inspired scriprures.",
                "These are books accepted by some sect and rejected by others. Thus they are included in few versions.",
                "These are books accepted by some sect and rejected by others."
            ],
            "answer": "These are books accepted by some sect and rejected by others. Thus they are included in few versions.",
            "details": "These are books accepted by some sect and rejected by others. Thus they are included in few versions."
        },
        {
            "number": 205,
            "question": "In how many languages was the Bible originally written?",
            "options": [3, 7, 12, 4],
            "answer": 3,
            "details": "3 Hebrew, Greek and Aramaic"
        },
        {
            "number": 206,
            "question": "Who is the author of Pentateuch?",
            "options": ["John", "Moses", "David", "Jeremiah"],
            "answer": "Moses",
            "details": "Moses - The Pentateuch also called the Laws book"
        },
        {
            "number": 207,
            "question": "Which books of the New Testament are referred to as gospel books?",
            "options": ["Matthew - John", "Acts - 2Corithians", "2nd John - Revelation", "Philemon - 1 Peter"],
            "answer": "Matthew - John",
            "details": "Four(4) Matthew Matthew, Mark, Luke, John"
        },
        {
            "number": 208,
            "question": "What are the two longest words in the Bible?",
            "options": ["Melphibosheth and Adonibezek", "Methuselah and Rechabites", "Melchizedek and Abraham", "Mahershalahashbaz and Jonathelemrechokim"],
            "answer": "Mahershalahashbaz and Jonathelemrechokim",
            "details": "Mahershalahashbaz - Isaiah 8:1-3 and Jonathelemrechokim - Psalm 56"
        },
        {
            "number": 209,
            "question": "What is the name given to books which are not included in the Bible because they are are rejected by everyone? (false writing)",
            "options": [
                "Pseudopigrapha books",
                "These are books now in a complete Bible.\nThey are considered as inspired scriprures.",
                "These are books accepted by some sect and rejected by others. Thus they are included in few versions.",
                "These are books accepted by some sect and rejected by others."
            ],
            "answer": "Pseudopigrapha books",
            "details": "Pseudopigrapha books"
        }

    ],
    "Names of Jesus": [{
            "number": 1,
            "name": "Jesus",
            "verse": "Matt. 1:21"
        }, {
            "number": 2,
            "name": "Prince of Peace",
            "verse": "Isa. 9:6"
        }, {
            "number": 3,
            "name": "Mighty",
            "verse": "Isa. 9:6"
        }, {
            "number": 4,
            "name": "Wondeful",
            "verse": "Isa. 9:6"
        }, {
            "number": 5,
            "name": "Counsellor",
            "verse": "Isa. 9:6"
        }, {
            "number": 6,
            "name": "Advocate",
            "verse": "1 John 2:1"
        }, {
            "number": 7,
            "name": "Lord God",
            "verse": "Rev. 15:3"
        }, {
            "number": 8,
            "name": "Lamb of God",
            "verse": "John 1:29"
        }, {
            "number": 9,
            "name": "Lion of the tribe of Judah",
            "verse": "Rev. 5:5"
        }, {
            "number": 10,
            "name": "Author and finisher of our faith",
            "verse": "Heb. 12:2"
        }, {
            "number": 11,
            "name": "Son of God",
            "verse": "John 1:34"
        }, {
            "number": 12,
            "name": "Emmanuel",
            "verse": "Matt. 1:23"
        }, {
            "number": 13,
            "name": "Morning Star",
            "verse": "Rev. 22:16"
        }, {
            "number": 14,
            "name": "Chief Shepherd",
            "verse": "1 Pet. 5:4"
        }, {
            "number": 15,
            "name": "Sun of Righteousness",
            "verse": "Matt. 4:2"
        }, {
            "number": 16,
            "name": "The Alpha and Omega",
            "verse": "Rev. 1:18"
        }, {
            "number": 17,
            "name": "Light of the world",
            "verse": "John 8:12"
        }, {
            "number": 18,
            "name": "Dayspring",
            "verse": "Luke 1:78"
        }, {
            "number": 19,
            "name": "The way",
            "verse": "John 14:6"
        }, {
            "number": 20,
            "name": "The Life",
            "verse": "John 14:6"
        }, {
            "number": 21,
            "name": "The Truth",
            "verse": "John 14:6"
        }, {
            "number": 22,
            "name": "Ancient of days",
            "verse": "Dan. 7:9"
        }, {
            "number": 23,
            "name": "Last Adam",
            "verse": "Isa. 9:6"
        }, {
            "number": 24,
            "name": "Apostle of our profession",
            "verse": "Heb. 3:1"
        }, {
            "number": 25,
            "name": "A merciful high priest",
            "verse": "Heb. 2:17"
        }, {
            "number": 26,
            "name": "Branch",
            "verse": "Isa. 4:2"
        }, {
            "number": 27,
            "name": "Beloved son",
            "verse": "Matt. 2:15"
        }, {
            "number": 28,
            "name": "Bread of Life",
            "verse": "John 6:35"
        }, {
            "number": 29,
            "name": "Beginning of God's creation",
            "verse": "Rev. 3:4"
        }, {
            "number": 30,
            "name": "Captain of our Salvation",
            "verse": "Heb. 2:10"
        },
        {
            "number": 31,
            "name": "The Door",
            "verse": "John 10:7"
        }, {
            "number": 32,
            "name": "Dead but alive",
            "verse": "Rev. 2:8"
        }, {
            "number": 33,
            "name": "Eternal one",
            "verse": "Isa. 42:1"
        }, {
            "number": 34,
            "name": "Everlasting Father",
            "verse": "Isa. 9:6"
        }, {
            "number": 35,
            "name": "Elect of God",
            "verse": "John 5:28"
        }, {
            "number": 36,
            "name": "Fore-runner",
            "verse": "Heb. 6:20"
        }, {
            "number": 37,
            "name": "Faith and true",
            "verse": "Rev. 19:11"
        }, {
            "number": 38,
            "name": "Great High Priest",
            "verse": "Heb. 4:14"
        }, {
            "number": 39,
            "name": "God in the flesh",
            "verse": "1 Tim. 3:4"
        }, {
            "number": 40,
            "name": "Holy one",
            "verse": "Acts 4:14"
        },
        {
            "number": 41,
            "name": "Holy child",
            "verse": "Acts 4:24"
        }, {
            "number": 42,
            "name": "Healer",
            "verse": "1 Pet. 2:2"
        }, {
            "number": 43,
            "name": "Horn of salvation",
            "verse": "Lk 1:69"
        }, {
            "number": 44,
            "name": "Heir of all things",
            "verse": "Heb. 1:2"
        }, {
            "number": 45,
            "name": "Head of the church",
            "verse": "Eph. 1:22"
        }, {
            "number": 46,
            "name": "Lord of All",
            "verse": "Acts 10:36"
        }, {
            "number": 47,
            "name": "Image of the invisible God",
            "verse": "Col. 1:15"
        }, {
            "number": 48,
            "name": "First born of every creature",
            "verse": "Col. 1:15"
        }, {
            "number": 49,
            "name": "First born from the dead",
            "verse": "Col. 1:18"
        }, {
            "number": 50,
            "name": "The creator",
            "verse": "Col. 1:18"
        },
        {
            "number": 51,
            "name": "The mediator",
            "verse": "1 Tim. 2:15"
        }, {
            "number": 52,
            "name": "The Governor",
            "verse": "Matt. 2:6"
        }, {
            "number": 53,
            "name": "Redeemer",
            "verse": "Isa 60:16"
        }, {
            "number": 54,
            "name": "Messiah",
            "verse": "John 4:25"
        }, {
            "number": 55,
            "name": "Justifier",
            "verse": "Gal. 2:16"
        }, {
            "number": 56,
            "name": "Sanctifier",
            "verse": "John 17:19"
        }, {
            "number": 57,
            "name": "Divine servant",
            "verse": "Isa. 42:1"
        }, {
            "number": 58,
            "name": "Amen",
            "verse": "Rev. 3:14"
        }, {
            "number": 59,
            "name": "Good master",
            "verse": "John 13:13"
        }, {
            "number": 60,
            "name": "Word of God",
            "verse": "John 1:1"
        },
        {
            "number": 61,
            "name": "The resurrection and the life",
            "verse": "John 11:25"
        }, {
            "number": 62,
            "name": "Wisdom of God",
            "verse": "1 Cor. 1:25"
        }, {
            "number": 63,
            "name": "King of Kings",
            "verse": "Rev. 19:16"
        }, {
            "number": 64,
            "name": "Root of David",
            "verse": "Rev. 22:16"
        }, {
            "number": 65,
            "name": "Rock of offence",
            "verse": "Rom. 1:33"
        }, {
            "number": 66,
            "name": "commander",
            "verse": "Isa. 55:4"
        }, {
            "number": 67,
            "name": "Rose of Sharon",
            "verse": "Song of Solomon 2:1"
        }, {
            "number": 68,
            "name": "Son of Man",
            "verse": "Matt. 8:20"
        }, {
            "number": 69,
            "name": "Seed of woman",
            "verse": "Gen. 3:15"
        }, {
            "number": 70,
            "name": "Arm of the Lord",
            "verse": "Isa. 53:1"
        },
        {
            "number": 71,
            "name": "Glory of God",
            "verse": "Isa. 40:5"
        }, {
            "number": 72,
            "name": "Gift of God",
            "verse": "John 4:10"
        }, {
            "number": 73,
            "name": "True vine",
            "verse": "John 15:1"
        }, {
            "number": 74,
            "name": "Son of David",
            "verse": "Matt. 1:1"
        }, {
            "number": 75,
            "name": "Shepherd and bishop of our soul",
            "verse": "1 Pet. 2:25"
        }, {
            "number": 76,
            "name": "The Rock",
            "verse": "1 Cor. 10:4"
        }, {
            "number": 77,
            "name": "Prince of Life",
            "verse": "Acts 3:15"
        }, {
            "number": 78,
            "name": "Lord of Lords",
            "verse": "1 Tim. 6:15"
        }, {
            "number": 79,
            "name": "King of the Jews",
            "verse": "John 13:13"
        }, {
            "number": 80,
            "name": "Almighty",
            "verse": "Rev. 1:8"
        },
        {
            "number": 81,
            "name": "Deliverer",
            "verse": "Rom. 11:26"
        }, {
            "number": 82,
            "name": "God of Justice",
            "verse": "Isa. 11:4"
        }, {
            "number": 83,
            "name": "Great Prophet",
            "verse": "Luke 24:19"
        }, {
            "number": 84,
            "name": "Christ Jesus our Lord",
            "verse": "Romans 8:39"
        }, {
            "number": 85,
            "name": "Anoninted Preacher",
            "verse": "Isa. 61:1"
        }, {
            "number": 86,
            "name": "I am",
            "verse": "John 8:58"
        }, {
            "number": 87,
            "name": "Bridgeroom",
            "verse": "Matt. 9:1"
        }, {
            "number": 88,
            "name": "Conqueror of death",
            "verse": "Acts 2:24"
        }, {
            "number": 89,
            "name": "Conqueror of sin",
            "verse": "Rom. 8:3"
        }, {
            "number": 90,
            "name": "First begotten",
            "verse": "Rev. 1:5"
        },
        {
            "number": 91,
            "name": "Faithful witness",
            "verse": "Rev. 19:6"
        }, {
            "number": 92,
            "name": "Omnipontent",
            "verse": "Isa. 11:1"
        }, {
            "number": 93,
            "name": "Rod of Jesus",
            "verse": "Isa. 11:1"
        }, {
            "number": 94,
            "name": "Saviour",
            "verse": "Matt. 1:21"
        }, {
            "number": 95,
            "name": "The Lily of the valley",
            "verse": "Songs of Solomon 2:1"
        }, {
            "number": 96,
            "name": "Holy one of Israel",
            "verse": "Isa. 41:14"
        }, {
            "number": 97,
            "name": "Great provider",
            "verse": "Matt. 15:36"
        }, {
            "number": 98,
            "name": "Chief cornestone",
            "verse": "Eph. 2:20"
        }, {
            "number": 99,
            "name": "Everlasting Ruler",
            "verse": "Dan. 7:14"
        }, {
            "number": 100,
            "name": "Burden bearer",
            "verse": "Isa. 53:4"
        },
        {
            "number": 101,
            "name": "Omnipresent",
            "verse": "Matt. 18:20"
        }, {
            "number": 102,
            "name": "Omniscient",
            "verse": "John 4:29"
        }
    ],
    "Professional Names of Jesus Christ": [{
            "number": 1,
            "question": "Archeologists call Him",
            "answer": "The beginning",
            "verse": "John 1:1"
        },
        {
            "number": 2,
            "question": "Animal Scientists call Him",
            "answer": "The Good Shepherd",
            "verse": "1 Pet. 5:4"
        },
        {
            "number": 3,
            "question": "Botanists call Him",
            "answer": "The tree of life",
            "verse": ""
        },
        {
            "number": 4,
            "question": "Food scientists call Him",
            "answer": "The Bread of life",
            "verse": "John 6:8"
        },
        {
            "number": 5,
            "question": "Carpenters call Him",
            "answer": "The Door",
            "verse": "John 10:7"
        },
        {
            "number": 6,
            "question": "Zoologists call Him",
            "answer": "The lion of the tribe of Judah",
            "verse": "Rev. 5:5"
        },
        {
            "number": 7,
            "question": "Sociologists call Him",
            "answer": "The love of God",
            "verse": "John 3:16"
        },
        {
            "number": 8,
            "question": "Medical Doctors call Him",
            "answer": "The Great Physician",
            "verse": "Luke 8:4, Exo. 15:26"
        },
        {
            "number": 9,
            "question": "Morticians call Him",
            "answer": "The Risen one",
            "verse": "Luke 24"
        },
        {
            "number": 10,
            "question": "Photographers call Him",
            "answer": "The image",
            "verse": "John 14:9, Col. 1:15"
        },
        {
            "number": 11,
            "question": "Sportsmen call Him",
            "answer": "The strength and Energizer",
            "verse": "Neh. 8:10"
        },
        {
            "number": 12,
            "question": "Industrialists call Him",
            "answer": "The great supplier",
            "verse": "Phil. 4:19"
        },
        {
            "number": 13,
            "question": "Lawyers call Him",
            "answer": "The mediator/Advocate",
            "verse": "1Tim. 2:5, 1John 2:1"
        },
        {
            "number": 14,
            "question": "Oceanographers call Him",
            "answer": "The River of living water",
            "verse": "John 4:10"
        }, {
            "number": 15,
            "question": "Horticulturists call Him",
            "answer": "The first fruit",
            "verse": "1 Cor. 15:12"
        },
        {
            "number": 16,
            "question": "Transporters call Him",
            "answer": "The way",
            "verse": "John 14:6"
        },
        {
            "number": 17,
            "question": "Administrators call Him",
            "answer": "The Governor",
            "verse": "Matt. 2:6"
        },
        {
            "number": 18,
            "question": "Journalists call Him",
            "answer": "The truth",
            "verse": "John 14:6"
        },
        {
            "number": 19,
            "question": "Biologists call Him",
            "answer": "The life",
            "verse": "John 14:6"
        },
        {
            "number": 20,
            "question": "Gardeners call Him",
            "answer": "The Rose of Sharon",
            "verse": "Songs of Solomon 2:1"
        },
        {
            "number": 21,
            "question": "To the Governor call Him",
            "answer": "The supreme Authority",
            "verse": ""
        },
        {
            "number": 22,
            "question": "Professors call Him",
            "answer": "The wisdom of God",
            "verse": "1 Cor. 1:24"
        },
        {
            "number": 23,
            "question": "Theologians call Him",
            "answer": "The baptizer",
            "verse": "John 1:33"
        },
        {
            "number": 24,
            "question": "Evangelists call Him",
            "answer": "The soul winner",
            "verse": "John 4:7-12"
        }, {
            "number": 25,
            "question": "Publishers refer to Him",
            "answer": "The Author",
            "verse": "Heb. 12:2"
        },
        {
            "number": 26,
            "question": "Architects call Him",
            "answer": "The Chief Cornerstone",
            "verse": "Eph. 2:20"
        },
        {
            "number": 27,
            "question": "Footballers call Him",
            "answer": "The Captain",
            "verse": "Heb. 2:10"
        },
        {
            "number": 28,
            "question": "Judges call Him",
            "answer": "The Righteous Judge",
            "verse": "Isaiah 11:4"
        },
        {
            "number": 29,
            "question": "Electrical Engineers call Him",
            "answer": "The light of the World",
            "verse": "John 8:12"
        }
    ],
    "Names of God": [{
            "number": 1,
            "question": "JEHOVAH EL-SHADDAI",
            "answer": "My all sufficient Almighty God",
            "verse": "Gen. 17:1"
        },
        {
            "number": 2,
            "question": "JEHOVAH HOSEENU",
            "answer": "The Lord my maker",
            "verse": "Ps 95"
        },
        {
            "number": 3,
            "question": "JEHOVAH ELOHEENU",
            "answer": "The Lord my God",
            "verse": "Psalms 99:5"
        },
        {
            "number": 4,
            "question": "JEHOVAH SHALOM",
            "answer": "The Lord my peace",
            "verse": "Jud 6:24"
        },
        {
            "number": 5,
            "question": "JEHOVAH NISSI",
            "answer": "The Lord my banner",
            "verse": "Exo. 17:6"
        },
        {
            "number": 6,
            "question": "JEHOVAH ELOLAM",
            "answer": "The everlasting God",
            "verse": "Gen. 21:23"
        },
        {
            "number": 7,
            "question": "JEHOVAH ELOHEKA",
            "answer": "The Lord my God",
            "verse": "eXO. 20:2"
        },
        {
            "number": 8,
            "question": "JEHOVAH SABOATH",
            "answer": "The Lord of Host",
            "verse": "1 Sam. 1:3"
        },
        {
            "number": 9,
            "question": "JEHOVAH SHAMMAH",
            "answer": "The Lord is present",
            "verse": "Ezek. 40:35"
        },
        {
            "number": 10,
            "question": "JEHOVAH  ELOHIM",
            "answer": "The Eternal Creator",
            "verse": "Gen. 1:1"
        },
        {
            "number": 11,
            "question": "JEHOVAH MEKADDISHKEM",
            "answer": "The Lord my sancifier",
            "verse": "Exo. 31:12"
        },
        {
            "number": 12,
            "question": "JEHOVAH RAPHA",
            "answer": "The Lord my healer",
            "verse": "Exo. 15:26"
        },
        {
            "number": 13,
            "question": "JEHOVAH EYON",
            "answer": "The Lord most High",
            "verse": "Gen. 40:35"
        },
        {
            "number": 14,
            "question": "JEHOVAH JIREH",
            "answer": "The Lord my provider",
            "verse": "Gen. 22:14"
        }, {
            "number": 15,
            "question": "JEHOVAH ADONAI",
            "answer": "My Sovereign God",
            "verse": "Gen. 15:2"
        },
        {
            "number": 16,
            "question": "JEHOVAH ELGIBBOR",
            "answer": "My mighty God",
            "verse": "Isaiah 9:6"
        },
        {
            "number": 17,
            "question": "JEHOVAH ROHI",
            "answer": "The Lord is my Shepherd",
            "verse": "Psalms 23:1"
        },
        {
            "number": 18,
            "question": "JEHOVAH TSIDKENU",
            "answer": "The Lord my righteousness",
            "verse": "Jeremiah 23:6"
        }
    ]
}]